Bonus Short Stories

Elemental☆Bunny

It was the beginning of September in Japan, on a Sunday shortly after summer break ended for high school third years. On this day, Miharu was visiting the apartment Satsuki lived in by herself.

“Welcome, Miharu. Come in, come in.”

“Thanks for letting me visit.”

Satsuki showed Miharu inside her room. There was a bed and a hanger rack packed tight with clothes.

“Now, let’s get you ready,” Satsuki said with a giggle.

“A-Amazing...” Miharu swallowed and looked around the room. There were cosplay outfits everywhere.

“You can pick out any outfit you like.”

“Thank you... But are you sure about this?”

“Yeah. They’re the cosplay outfits an upperclassman’s circle used at the university’s school festival last year, but they’re not participating this year. So no one’s wearing them anyway.”

So that’s why Miharu could borrow them.

“With this many outfits, I’m sure there’ll be a good one for you to wear in the school festival’s beauty pageant.”

Incidentally, Miharu was going to participate in the beauty pageant for their school festival. It was tradition for the third years to select one person from their class, and while Miharu had no intention of volunteering herself, she ended up being selected. The contest required participants to wear a cosplay outfit, so she went to Satsuki—who had entered last year—for advice, resulting in this visit.

“Now that we’re here, let’s find the one that suits you the best.”

“N-No, I’d prefer the one that stands out the least...” Miharu said reluctantly.

“Nah, you’re sure to win no matter what you wear. If you’d entered last year or the year before, you would have been the winner for sure.” Satsuki laughed at Miharu with a mischievous smile.

Miharu shook her head furiously. “Th-That’s not true.”

“I’ll be going to watch, so I’m looking forward to it too. Now, let’s choose! I haven’t checked them all myself, so there are still some in these cardboard boxes.” With that, Satsuki eagerly started opening the sealed boxes.

“Y-You seem to be having fun, Satsuki...”

“Well, of course. I get to see you try on all kinds of outfits.”

“D-Do I have to try them on...?”

“Yes. You’ll be upset on the day of the pageant if it doesn’t fit, no?”

“R-Right...” Miharu hung her head in resignation and nodded.

“Something too flashy wouldn’t suit you, but we shouldn’t let ourselves be biased while choosing either. Oh, but this one is a little...whew...”

The outfit Satsuki pulled out of a box while talking was a bunny girl outfit. It was white in color with matching bunny ears.

“University students dress this radically...?” Miharu’s face instantly turned bright red.

“Aha ha... I’m sure this one wasn’t used. It says ‘rejected’ on the box too. There are a bunch of other risque outfits in here.”

“Th-Then let’s not look at that box any further,” Miharu protested firmly.

“Right. But since we’re here already...I’d really like to see you try some on,” Satsuki pleaded with a teasing smile on her face.

“N-No way.”

“What if we called Haruto here to watch?”

“That’s even worse!”

“But I bet Haruto would want to see you wearing a bunny girl outfit...”

“I-I highly doubt that...”

“Then let’s ask him directly! If he says he wants to see it, you have to wear it! Okay, it’s decided!” As soon as she said that, Satsuki whipped out her smartphone.

“Wh-Wha?!”

“Aaand sent!”

While Miharu was hesitating in confusion, Satsuki had texted the message, “Don’t you want to see Miharu in a bunny girl outfit?”

Haruto’s reply arrived several minutes later, but he and Satsuki are the only ones who know whether or not Miharu wore the outfit.

Chapter 1: Life in the Galarc Kingdom

Meanwhile, in the mansion Rio was given by King Francois as Haruto Amakawa, honorary knight...

Ten days had passed since Rio started living with the members of the stone house. It was past noon, and Charlotte was once again visiting the estate. Satsuki, Liselotte, Christina, and Flora accompanied her.

Charlotte wet her throat with the tea that was served, then addressed Rio and Celia seated across from her sofa. “I am here today to give you two a job request.”

“Us?” Rio and Celia exchanged a look before answering together.

“Yes. It’s an official request from the kingdom, so you’ll naturally be compensated for it. The terms of work can be limited to while you’re in the capital. If you could give it your consideration with these details in mind, I would appreciate it,” Charlotte said, prefacing her explanation with emphasis that the job was voluntary.

“What kind of job is it...?”

“I’d like the two of you to become temporary instructors. I’m hoping for Lady Celia to hold a special class on sorcery at the Galarc Royal Academy, while Sir Haruto teaches close combat to a class prepared by us.”

“I understand Celia with her lecturer experience from the Beltrum Royal Academy, but I’ve never taught a class before.”

“Hee hee, that is a needless fear. I’m positive teaching won’t be a problem for someone of your abilities.” Rio was unsure of himself, but Charlotte gave her approval with full confidence.

“It’s a great honor to hear that, but I am unfamiliar with the sword styles and martial arts of the Galarc Kingdom.”

“That isn’t a problem either. What I’m requesting isn’t for you to teach technical basics to beginners, but to give more practical instruction to people with combat experience. There’ll be people specializing in various weapons and styles of fighting.”

“I see...” Rio muttered in thought.

He had previously taught Masato, who was completely new to combat, as well as the warriors of the spirit folk village, who had no experience in hand-to-hand combat due to their lack of infighting. But teaching the career soldiers of Galarc and the Restoration who already possessed all the required knowledge would be a different matter. Of course, there’d probably be people of nobility among them, so he wasn’t sure how much he’d be able to teach them.

“I know you have a strong sense of responsibility, so I understand if you won’t agree without careful consideration. But you don’t have to think so hard about it—you can treat it like a mock battle or a light sparring match. The reason why this job came up this time is because many have expressed a desire to spar with the Honorary Knight Sir Haruto.”

“While I wouldn’t refuse a light sparring match...do you know roughly how many people will be in attendance at this class?”

“I’m thinking of limiting it to a maximum of twenty people at first. I imagine whoever is free at the time will be in attendance, but I will take responsibility for the selection of attendees, so you don’t need to worry in that regard.”

Charlotte grinned boldly, as though to say she wouldn’t allow anyone to pull anything funny. As one would expect, she had considered all the points Rio could possibly find concerning. Rio was impressed by her prudence, and his expression softened in amusement.

“It may be better to reduce that number if I’m to face everyone myself, but if the attendees don’t mind sparring with each other, then that works too.”

“Whether it’s one-on-one, or an all-out brawl, I’ll leave it to you to decide based on the number of attendees at the class at the time.”

“I see. In that case...”

It may be possible to maintain a proper lecture format that way. Whether the attendees will be satisfied with that is a different matter, though...

“For now, the attendees of the first class are pretty much decided already, so how about you give it a try? You can decide if you want to continue with future classes after that,” Charlotte suggested.

Apparently, she had arranged everything regarding the first class in preparation for Rio’s agreement. Since she had gone through so much trouble before approaching with the request, Rio found it hard to refuse. Or rather, he found himself wanting to repay her for her consideration.

“I understand... I’ll give it a try,” Rio said, accepting the request.

“Thank you. I believed you would say that, Sir Haruto. In that case, the first class will be held—I’m so pleased. I can’t wait to see your gallant figure again,” Charlotte smiled in delight. Charlotte replied gleefully, smiling in delight.

“You’re in high spirits, Char.”

“Hee hee. You said it’d be interesting yourself, Lady Satsuki.”

Satsuki had been sitting in silence as they talked but joined the conversation with a giggle. Charlotte had also given her reply in a cheery mood.

“Incidentally, who’ll be attending the first class?” Rio asked, looking at Satsuki.

“First, Lady Satsuki will be there. Attending from Galarc will be several of my knights and Liselotte’s attendants. Some of Princess Christina and Princess Flora’s female knights will also be attending from the Restoration side,” Charlotte answered with a look at Christina and Liselotte.

“Princess Charlotte approached us with the offer. The Restoration will attend through Vanessa and some of her subordinates. They may cause you trouble, but please guide them well, Sir Amakawa,” Christina said with a nod.

“A few of my attendants who accompanied me to the capital will also be in attendance. Please teach them as well,” Liselotte continued with a bow.

“Which means there’ll be some familiar faces...” Rio was a little bothered by how they were all women. “I understand. I don’t know how well I’ll be able to teach them, but I’ll do my best,” he replied, straightening himself and nodding.

“As long as it’s okay with you, I’d like the first class to be held in a few days. Would that suit your circumstances? I’m thinking of holding it in the morning, after breakfast and before the afternoon...”

“I’ll be free as early as tomorrow at that time.”

“Really? Then let’s hold it tomorrow! If the others in your mansion would like to watch or participate, we can hold it in the square in the rear garden. I’ll drop by around nine o’clock in the morning.” Charlotte looked around at Latifa and everyone present.

“Yes! I’d love to go and watch!” Latifa raised her hand energetically.

“If Haruto’s teaching, I’d like to attend as a student.”

“I’m also interested.”

Sara raised her hand shyly, followed closely by Alma.

“The two of you are most welcome to join. That is fine, right?” Charlotte agreed readily, checking with Rio for confirmation.

“Yes, of course. In that case, you can take the class for most of the time, but could you act as my assistants when I need help?”

“Sure!” Sara agreed.

“Leave it to us,” Alma added.

“Aishia, you too.”

“Yup.” Aishia nodded without hesitation.

“That settles the matter of Sir Haruto’s special instruction. Lady Celia, what will you do about yours?” Charlotte summarized in satisfaction, then turned to Celia.

“There are a few things I’d like to confirm, but the fact that Princess Christina is here means you’ve cleared this with her, right?”

“Yes. Or rather, you’ve been temporarily transferred to Sir Amakawa right now, so the decision is up to you two,” Christina answered.

“Thank you. What kind of subjects are you expecting me to cover?” Celia asked Charlotte.

“Any subject is fine, but your students will range from upper elementary- to middle school-aged. Each class can be a complete course, or you can take several classes to cover a topic if you prefer. We can discuss that after taking into consideration the duration of Sir Haruto’s stay in Galarc.”

“I plan on staying for another month. If Celia agrees to teaching, please plan around that schedule,” Rio explained.

“If you could proceed with the arrangement of the classes, I’ll start thinking about my lesson plans.”

Thus, Celia decided to hold her special lectures as well.

◇　◇　◇

The next morning, in order to take Rio’s close combat class, people who crossed organization borders gathered on the mansion grounds.

Galarc Kingdom’s Second Princess Charlotte walked in the lead, guiding them. She was accompanied by her attendants and female knights behind her. Walking beside her were the Restoration’s Christina and Flora. They were similarly followed by their attendants and knights, including Vanessa. A little farther behind the princesses was Liselotte, daughter of Galarc’s Duke Cretia. She was accompanied by her attendants who also acted as her guards—Aria, Cosette, and Natalie.

In front of the gate were two female knights from Galarc. Rio had no retainers, and the hero and princess of the kingdom often visited his mansion, so the area was guarded by the castle’s knights.

Incidentally, since the mansion Rio was given was on the castle grounds, space was limited. Therefore, the mansion was located a stone’s throw away from the front gate. Instead, the rear garden had a bigger private space away from the public eye, and there was more than enough room to hold a sparring match with weapons.

In preparation for the arrival of the guests, a gazebo was set up in the garden towards the front gate for Rio and the others to relax in. (Satsuki had stayed over the night before, so she was at the mansion already.)

“Welcome, everyone.”

“Good morning, Sir Haruto. We’ve arrived as promised.”

“I’ve been waiting.”

Rio approached the group and placed his right hand over his chest, welcoming them.

“Let’s get straight to the point. If the preparations are complete, please begin teaching.”

Since they were limited on time, they got straight to business upon arrival.

“I understand. Please, follow me.”

Rio led the party to the rear garden. There was an even larger gazebo in the back, which he stopped by first. Wooden weapons for the mock battles had been brought over the day before and were lined in front of the gazebo.

“Anyone who wishes to observe, please head under the gazebo. Those participating in the class, please select your best weapon out of those available and come this way.”

Rio then picked up the wooden sword leaning beside him and walked a short distance away. Aishia and Satsuki picked up wooden spears and went after him, followed by Sara, who picked up two wooden daggers, and Alma, who chose a wooden mace.

Then, the rest of the participants, which included Vanessa, Aria, Cosette, Natalie, and the others, each selected their own weapon and followed them.

“Everyone else, please come this way.”

At Celia’s prompting, Charlotte and the others made their way under the gazebo. There was a table and chairs set up underneath where everyone other than the attendants sat down to watch Rio’s class.

In the meantime, the participants had already distanced themselves sufficiently from the gazebo.

“Around here should do.” Rio, who had been walking in the lead, came to a stop and turned around to face the knights and attendants. Aishia, Sara, and Alma stood beside him.

“It’s okay for me to be on this side, right?” Satsuki checked with Rio before lining up among Aria and the others.

“Yes.”

The participants are Satsuki, five knights from Galarc, five knights from the Restoration, and three of Liselotte’s attendants. Then there’s Aishia, Sara, and Alma. A total of seventeen people. And they’re really all women...

After looking around at everyone, Rio felt a little awkward. Being the only man in a group of women was rather wearing on the mind. The observers under the gazebo were also women, so he felt like he had walked into an all-girls school alone.

However, Rio guessed Charlotte had actually limited her selection of participants to women for his sake... Or rather, for the sake of Latifa and the others who were living in the mansion. After telling her they weren’t used to being around nobility, she probably assumed they’d be more comfortable around members of the same sex and acted out of consideration. The people here were also somewhat familiar faces that could usually be seen protecting Charlotte and Christina. That being said...

“My name is Haruto Amakawa. I am honored to be able to instruct you all in close combat at the request of Princess Charlotte.”

There were many he hadn’t spoken to before, so Rio gave a self-introduction. At that, the participants all drew their gazes to him. Some looked at him with curiosity, some looked at him with admiration, and some looked at him in evaluation.

“These three are my friends: Aishia, Sara, and Alma. They’ll be participating in the class as my assistants. We spar with each other on a regular basis, so I can guarantee that the three of them are good opponents. The hero, Lady Satsuki, will also be participating along with everyone.”

At Rio’s introduction, Sara and Alma bowed their heads first.

“I’m Satsuki. I’d appreciate it if you interacted with me without all the stiff hero formalities. Nice to meet you,” Satsuki said. However, the position of those present wouldn’t allow them to accept her words so naively, and they all responded with a respectful bow of their heads.

I guess I’ll have to work on the rest over the course of the sparring matches, Satsuki thought with a strained smile when she saw them react in such a way.

“The purpose of this class is to teach close combat, so I’m thinking of focusing the class on mock battles. To be honest, I don’t have much confidence in my abilities to instruct everyone. But since I’ve agreed to do this already, I will take responsibility and do my best. Now... Our time is limited, so let’s begin.”

Rio declared the start of the lesson. He had thought of the lesson plan yesterday, but he lacked teaching experience. He had no choice but to figure things out as he went along. Now that he felt aware of that all over again, his expression stiffened with slight nervousness.

“I’d like to begin by measuring everyone’s abilities, so I’m going to face each of you one by one. The match will be suspended as soon as I measure your strength, but can also end with an effective blow. So please come at me with the intention of hitting me. Magic and sorcery is allowed in the form of physical ability enhancement. The only necessity is a sign signaling the start, so will you be willing to act as umpire, Sara?”

“Yes. Leave it to me.” Sara stepped forward at Rio’s request. Hearing they would start with sparring made the participants all pull themselves together. They were probably drawn to the opportunity to spar with Rio, who had many military achievements under his belt. They wanted to measure his abilities just as much as—if not more than—he wanted to know theirs.

“Then, my first opponent will be...”

Rio looked around at the participants.

“Please allow me.” One of the knights from the Galarc Kingdom immediately raised her hand. Everyone’s attention gathered on her.

“You’re...”

She seemed to be in her early twenties. She normally accompanied Charlotte around the place and left an impression on Rio for occasionally sending him scrutinizing looks.

“I’m Louise Sharon, knight of the Galarc Kingdom and captain of Princess Charlotte’s personal guards.”

“Then, first will be Dame Sharon. It’s nice to meet you...not for the first time, but I believe this is our first proper greeting. Let’s have a good match.”

“Agreed,” Louise replied to Rio with a light bow.

“This way, please.” Rio led her a short distance away from the rest of the group. Louise gazed at his back while following him—

Say, Louise. I want you to face Sir Haruto before anyone else tomorrow. If you lose to him as the captain, your entire squad will have to accept him, right?

—And recalled the words Charlotte had said to her yesterday. Her words didn’t hold an ounce of doubt for Haruto’s victory, but it didn’t hurt her pride as a soldier. As a knight, Louise Sharon considered her master’s words to be absolute. Whatever Charlotte said, went.

However, she did have thoughts about Haruto.

Sir Haruto Amakawa. The person Princess Charlotte loves...

Louise worshipped Charlotte. She was dotingly fond of her. She had been assigned to protect Charlotte since she was young, watching over her growth until now. She had kept her feelings secret to avoid disrespect, but there was no way she didn’t find her adorable. One could say she was in love with Charlotte—that was how much she felt for her. Yet when it came to Charlotte—

Say, Louise. When do you think Sir Haruto will return?

Say, Louise. Sir Haruto is really amazing.

Say, Louise. Sir Haruto mentioned this today...

With the face of an infatuated maiden, she only spoke of a single man to Louise every day. It was as though the one she loved had fallen in love with someone else—there was no way she felt indifferent to that.

Furthermore, Louise’s ardor had spread to her subordinates—all the knights protecting Charlotte had conflicted feelings about Rio.

Thus, Louise stared at Rio as though to say, “Can you really make Princess Charlotte happy? I won’t forgive you if you lay your hands on other women. Or rather, I won’t forgive you if you lay your hands on our adorable Princess Charlotte. Understood?” Her subordinates watched on from afar similarly.

Heh, things are about to get interesting. Charlotte saw through what her guards were thinking and smiled in delight as she watched things unfold.

She’s got a fierce look in her eyes... Rio had no idea what the knights were thinking but felt a little awkward when facing Louise’s gaze.

“Augendae Corporis. Please enhance yourself too, Dame Sharon.” He pulled himself together and recited the spell, activating the magic artifact he wore on his arm to enhance his physical abilities. A spell circle appeared, covering Rio’s body in light. Using spirit arts would put him at a physical advantage, so he didn’t just pretend to activate it before canceling it. He would fight on the same conditions.

“Okay. Augendae Corporis.”

Louise didn’t rely on an artifact like Rio and enhanced herself with magic.

“The rules are as I explained earlier. Feel free to use your weapon and fists to land one hit on me.”

“Understood. I don’t plan on holding back,” she said without hostility, but she stared at Rio sharply as she nodded.

“Good. Please don’t.”

“...” Rio replied with a refreshing smile. That seemed to catch Louise by surprise, as she frowned a bit upon seeing it.

He didn’t stop to think about the faint change in Louise’s expression and addressed Sara instead. “Shall we begin, then? Sara. If you could give the signal to start.”

“Okay. Begin when I count down from five. Are you ready?” Sara checked.

“Yes.”

“At any time.”

The two of them nodded.

“Five, four, three, two, one. Begin!”

Louise silently burst into a run as soon as the signal was given, approaching Rio. The distance between them had been five meters to start, but the gap was closed in an instant. She proceeded to swing her wooden sword in an efficient move, slashing at him. However, Rio had perfectly seen through her trajectory and stepped forward to parry Louise’s sword before she could build up enough momentum. Louise had also shifted her center of gravity in order to step forward, so she was knocked off balance as soon as her sword was deflected, killing her momentum completely.

It was a perfectly timed parry. If it were one moment later, Louise would have enough weight leaning forward to prevent herself from being knocked back.

Guh... This is bad. He’s going to counterattack.

Louise broke out in a cold sweat, sensing her defeat early on in the match. However, Rio didn’t step forward—on the contrary, he stepped back and adjusted his hold on his wooden sword.

“Why didn’t you pursue me with a follow-up attack just now...?” Louise asked dubiously.

It was only for a brief moment, but she had been defenseless in the time it took her to regain balance. She knew Rio wasn’t the kind of opponent who would let such an opening slip by based on his parry just now, which was why she found it questionable.

“This is a sparring match for me to learn your abilities, not to become victorious.”

“Honestly, I felt quite a gap in ability just from that first blow... Though I charged at you with a test strike, my level of skill was shameful,” Louise said with a vexed look. It was precisely because she was an experienced fighter that she could feel the differences in their skill all the more keenly.

“That’s not true. It was a polished move with no movements put to waste. Although that just made the movement easier to predict... And if I had swung any later, I would have missed the timing to make a counterattack,” Rio said matter-of-factly.

If his timing had been off by an instant, he would have lost the chance to counter. It’s hard to believe he saw through the timing and swung his sword while aiming for it... But no matter how I look at it, he aimed for that moment. Just what kind of combat sense does he have? It’s beyond what I imagined.

She had been swinging with her body physically enhanced, so the correct timing would’ve been shorter than a second. With that analysis, Louise fell speechless.

“If there’s nothing else, let’s resume the match. Feel free to come at me whenever.”

“Fine...”

Louise nodded awkwardly, taking a deep breath to focus on the battle again.

◇　◇　◇

Rio sparred with the participants one after another. He had already finished matches against eleven of them, and he was yet to let anyone land a hit on him. Roughly half an hour later, he was sparring with Liselotte’s attendant, Natalie, as his twelfth opponent.

He’s fought against ten knights of Galarc and the Restoration in successive matches, yet he hasn’t lost a single one. Duke Cretia’s attendants are as skilled as the rumors said too...

Smiling, Louise had a look of half amazement and half shock as she intently observed Rio winning match after match. The other knights were also watching the battles quietly with serious expressions. Everyone present had diligently trained themselves as soldiers, so they were all vexed that they were no match for him and watched for any moves they could learn from him.

Meanwhile, Cosette and Aria were standing side by side to watch their colleague fight.

“Natalie’s dancing in the palm of his hand.”

“Just like you were moments ago, you mean,” Aria pointed out.

Indeed, in Cosette’s match with Rio, she had exerted all her stamina helplessly until the match ended without her ever making a comeback.

“Well, yeah. Still, I knew he was strong, but I didn’t think he’d be this strong without his enchanted sword... The name he’s made for himself is the real deal. His skills were beyond what I imagined when I fought him too. He’s wonderful, honestly.”

Cosette wasn’t particularly bothered by how helpless she had been—in fact, she gazed at Rio dreamily as she spoke. Aria watched her colleague with a tired sigh.

“Of course he is. It’d be impossible to defeat the King’s Sword with just an enchanted sword if you didn’t have the sword skills to back it up. Talent and effort—you can only reach his level at such a young age when you’re blessed with both these factors.”

“A hardworking genius, huh? Does that mean a genius like you would be able to land a hit on him?”

“I’m not a genius, but there’s also no telling until we actually cross swords.” Aria frowned slightly, not particularly fond of being called a genius.

“It’ll be your turn next. The strongest, demon-like head attendant versus Sir Haruto. I’m looking forward to seeing who can best whom. Look, the match is almost over,” Cosette said as she watched on.

Natalie was closing in on Rio resolutely, dual wooden daggers wielded in her hands. Rio was holding back his counterattacks to observe her movements better, so the attacks were being dealt one-sidedly from Natalie’s side.

However, Rio continuously evaded her attacks with minimal movement, making him less out of breath than her despite being the one fighting one opponent after another. It was only a matter of time until their match would conclude.

“She’s getting worked up by the lack of opportunities to attack. She’s always hated losing.”

A regular bystander wouldn’t be able to tell Natalie was getting frustrated, as she was still swinging her dagger with a serious expression. But being that she was her colleague, Cosette could see through her.

“Let’s stop here.”

Rio lowered his sword, calling for the end of the match.

Natalie looked like she wanted to fight more, but her obedient personality made her lower her daggers without protest. She nodded after a pause. “All right.”

“I’m sure there’ll be more chances to spar in the future, so until then.” Rio seemed to sense some kind of emotion from Natalie’s expression, making him smile.

“R-Right.” Natalie nodded in embarrassment, noting the fact that she’d been seen through.

“Aria is last, then. Please come forward,” Rio shouted, calling Aria over from a fair distance away.

Shortly after, Aria took Natalie’s place in front of Rio, and they stood five meters apart from one another.

“Let’s have a good match.”

“Yes, let’s indeed.” Rio returned the polite bow Aria sent his way.

“Once you’re ready, we’ll begin at the count of five. Please enhance your physical abilities with magic or sorcery.”

“I’m ready whenever. Augendae Corporis.”

“I’m ready too. Augendae Corporis.”

“I’ll start the countdown then. Five, four, three, two, one. Begin!”

At Sara’s signal, the match began.

Aria immediately ran at Rio. The moment she did, she swung her wooden sword at him, catching him at just the right timing. Even an experienced warrior would have found such a movement difficult to react to, much less an amateur, but Rio deflected the attack with a swing of his blade. But blocking just the first attack wasn’t enough to stop Aria’s movements; with a swift and graceful arm, she swung her sword in another attempt to hit Rio. That movement even made Sara’s eyes widen in awe.

“Th-That doesn’t count! It doesn’t count as a kiss! That was on the fingers. The fingers!” Latifa immediately protested.

“Then I wish to kiss him on the lips next.” Charlotte’s heated gaze was fixed on Rio’s mouth.

“Onii-chan!” Latifa tugged on Rio’s arm, trying to pull him away from Charlotte.

“Hey now, you know you can’t do that, Char. You’re an unmarried princess. We’ll pretend we didn’t see that just now, but you need to leave it at that. Okay?” Satsuki had been watching the series of events in shock, but Latifa’s yell shocked her back into her senses, allowing her to warn Charlotte with a sigh.

“You should listen to Satsuki.” Thanks to Satsuki’s intervention, Rio was able to distance himself from Charlotte this time. In exchange, Latifa clung to him instead.

I’m so tired, and we haven’t even left yet.

They had yet to depart, but Rio felt as exhausted as the end of the journey.

“Get in the horse carriage before Char does anything else strange, Haruto.” Satsuki urged him towards the nearby carriage with a sigh.

“If you would excuse me, then. Shall we go?”

Rio looked at Miharu, Celia, and Aishia, who were the closest nearby. Finally, he looked down at Latifa clinging to his left arm and patted her head. With some final parting words, they boarded the carriage and departed.

“I’m so envious of Lady Suzune. Lady Celia, Lady Miharu, Lady Aishia...” Charlotte mumbled sadly while watching the carriage go.

Watching her made Satsuki feel a little sad too, so she smiled brightly. “Times like this call for a bathing session together. Haruto said we were free to use his mansion whenever, so let’s make the most of it. I’ll wash your back for you.”

◇　◇　◇

After the carriage reached the noble district gate, Rio and the others disembarked and made their way out of the capital on foot. They proceeded down the main road out of the city until there was no one else around, then headed off the road towards the stone house where the spirit folk girls were waiting.

When they stepped past the barrier around the house, Sara and the others immediately came out.

“Welcome back.”

“Shouldn’t you be saying ‘I’m home’ to Miharu and Latifa instead?” Alma said, pointing out how they were the ones who had returned from the village.

“That’s true... But everyone’s also returning to the stone house.”

“Hee hee, doesn’t it work both ways?” Orphia suggested in amusement.

“We’re home! And welcome back! Sara, Orphia, Alma, long time no see!” Latifa called out to them energetically, raising a hand.

“It’s good to see the three of you well,” Miharu said.

“Having everyone gather in the stone house really feels like coming home,” Celia added.

“While it’d be nice to take a break like this...is it okay if we head for the village right away?” Rio asked everyone from where he stood beside Aishia.

“Sure. I want to see the village anyway,” Celia said, nodding with strong interest and excitement.

“We’re happy to hear you’re so excited to go to our village.” Sara grinned a little bashfully.

“It’s going to be so fluffy! A fluffy paradise! I want to touch the fur of all kinds of people there.”

“Ah ha ha!”

Everyone laughed in amusement.

“So let’s get going already.” Embarrassed, Celia blushed and urged them to depart.

“I’ll put away the house, then. Conditum.”

Orphia used the Time-Space Cache equipped on her arm to collect the stone house. The area where it stood immediately turned into empty space.

“Then I shall use the teleport crystal. There’s a range to the effect, so please stay as close to me as possible. Especially since there’s many of us.”

“Okay!” Latifa took the lead by hugging Rio’s right arm, while Aishia pressed herself up against him from the other side.

There’s no need to be this close, though...

The effective range was around three meters in radius, so there was no need for seven people to pack themselves together so tightly. Rio’s expression stiffened in shyness, and he lowered his gaze uneasily. “O-Okay. Is this good?”

Feeling competitive against Aishia and Latifa, Celia clung to Rio from the front. The height gap between them meant her face was touching him in the chest.

“Y-Yes...”

Taken aback, Rio nodded uncomfortably. “...”

The remaining free space was Rio’s back. Miharu’s, Sara’s, Orphia’s, and Alma’s gazes naturally gathered on that point. And the first one to move was...all four of them. However, the one who started the closest to Rio’s back was Miharu. The other three were standing in front of him, so they took an extra moment to go around.

“M-Miharu...?”

At the unexpected sensation pressing against his back, Rio’s eyes widened. Since Sara and the others were in front of him, the only one who could possibly be behind him was Miharu—but that was exactly what was surprising to Rio. Miharu had never tried to cling to him before. He couldn’t help turning his neck to look behind him.

“I-I would appreciate it...if you didn’t look behind you...”

But Miharu’s trembling voice stopped him. Her face was dyed the deep shade of a ripe peach. She didn’t want Rio to see her like that.

“Wow, Miharu, your face is bright red,” Latifa said with wide eyes.

“I-It’s not red, though?” Miharu’s denial came out in a rather high-pitched voice. She could feel the heat from her own face.

“Umm, there’s no need to be pressed so close...” Rio tried to protest hesitantly.

“Everyone’s clinging too closely to Rio!”

“Isn’t it unfair that we’re left out, Sara?”

“Yes! Wait, no—?!”

“It’s fine. Please press together closer, or there’ll be no room for us.”

Sara, Orphia, and Alma crowded forward, making things even noisier and more cramped.

I-I can’t move...

Normally, Rio was capable of moving at rapid speeds to evade all enemy attacks, but he was completely helpless at this point. He was blocked in on all sides.

Rio tried to move his limbs a little, but the sensation of things that shouldn’t be touched was transmitted back to him. The noisy sounds of ‘I prefer that, Sara!’ and ‘Your face is too close, Aishia!’ echoed around him.

“I said there’s no need to be this close...”

No one responded to Rio’s reserved opinion.

Wh-Whatever. Let’s just teleport away from here as quickly as possible, Rio said to himself, clearing his mind so that he could make a decision.

“R-Right, let’s go now. I’m going to say the spell. Transilio.”

He chanted the spell and activated the teleport crystal in his hand. The next moment, space spiraled and warped around Rio. Another moment later, the scenery changed completely. They had moved from the forest at Galarc’s outskirts to the spirit folk village deep within the Wilderness. Position-wise, they were located one or two minutes’ flight from the village town hall.

There was a time difference between the Strahl region and the village, but it was still bright where they had teleported to. Sunlight filtered through the trees and across the forest. There was a spring beside them and a blue sky extending above their heads.

At an ordinary time, this would have been a calm and peaceful space. However, since the women in the group had been making a fuss up until the teleportation, they hadn’t noticed that they had arrived. This caused their loud voices to echo through the forest.

“We’ve arrived...” Rio said to the girls that were still clinging onto him with a sigh. He then looked around to confirm that they had teleported successfully—which was when he noticed a gaze from a certain direction.

Several people wearing what looked like traditional Japanese clothing were seated on the rocky bank of the spring. They were surprised by the sudden arrival of Rio and the girls—or perhaps they were surprised to see so many beautiful girls clinging to Rio—as they were blinking in wonder.

Why are they here...?

Rio recognized some of the people among them—they were people who should have been at the next stop of their trip.

He froze in bewilderment. The girls clinging to him naturally noticed his gaze and looked the same way. As a result, Rio’s group and the people wearing kimonos stared at each other. Then, one man stood up from the group.

“Why are you here, Gouki?” Rio asked him. He was the senior warrior of the Karasuki Kingdom—Saga Gouki—and the former guard for Rio’s mother Ayame, with Rio’s father Zen.

“We were told you would appear by this spring if we waited here...” Gouki scratched at his cheek awkwardly, then stopped to stare closely at the girls surrounding Rio. “I see you’re in high demand, hmm? As expected of Princess Ayame and Zen’s son.” He burst out in hearty laughter.

“No, umm... This is... Ha ha.”

Rio tried to brush it off by laughing. Miharu, Celia, and Latifa watched on, wondering who the man was. Meanwhile, the three spirit folk girls who had returned earlier seemed aware of their identities, as they were watching Rio’s face instead. As a result, the air was rather awkward between them all.

“Don’t trouble Sir Rio, dear.”

Behind Gouki, his wife, Saga Kiyoko, scolded her husband in a cold tone. It was as though she were saying this wasn’t the time to be joking around.

“R-Right.” Gouki nodded awkwardly. “We were rejected by you once, but we hastened to join and serve you anyway. I know it is brazen of me to ask, but would you allow me another opportunity to convince you?” He lowered himself onto one knee, suddenly, appealing to Rio with humble reverence.

“Please, Sir Rio!” a young girl’s voice shouted. The one who had spoken was Gouki’s daughter, Saga Komomo. Beside her was her guard and attendant, Aoi.

“Komomo came along too, I see... And also...” Rio looked at the girl hidden behind Gouki and Komomo. There was a familiar boy immediately beside her.

“Shin and Sayo too...”

They were the siblings from the village Rio had lived in. Rio had said his farewells to them before leaving the Yagumo region, so why were they here? Rio had a serious look on his face as he contemplated the reason.

“Hey, Sayo. What are you hiding there for? Come on.”

“W-Wait, Shin...”

In a sullen tone, Shin grabbed Sayo by the hand and forcefully pulled her into a spot where Rio could see her better. Sayo met eyes with Celia and the others clinging to Rio for a brief second, then ducked her head to avert her gaze with a nauseated look.

“...”

At the sight of Sayo’s reaction, the girls surrounding Rio were all convinced that something had happened between them.

“Tch, have some more confidence.” Shin looked between Sayo and the girls beside Rio, then narrowed his eyes in a glare.

“At any rate, I’m glad to see you again. I was just thinking of returning to the Yagumo region, but how about we move somewhere else first? I’d like to greet the elders too.” Rio looked somewhat troubled, but eventually softened his expression into a smile.

“Of course. We’d be delighted.”

Gouki bowed his head deeply. Thus, the entire group relocated to the town hall first.

◇　◇　◇

At the town hall of the village, in a room on the highest floor...

Rio had his reunion with the elders: Syldora, Dominic, and Ursula. After they rejoiced in seeing each other again, Rio introduced Celia to them.

“Nice to meet you. I’m Celia Claire. Thank you for inviting me to the village.”

Celia stood up from her chair, lightly pinching at the hem of her dress to give a courteous bow. Her good upbringing was evident, making the elders and Gouki’s group widen their eyes.

“I am one of the head elders, the high elf Syldora. Welcome, teacher of Rio. These two are my fellow elders, fox werebeast Ursula and elder dwarf Dominic.”

“I’m Ursula. We’ve heard a lot about you from Rio. It seems Sara and the others have been in your company too. I hope you enjoy your time with us.”

“Welcome, little miss!”

And so, the elders all welcomed Celia.

“Little... Ah, thank you very much.” Celia’s eyes widened faintly at being called “little miss,” but then she giggled happily.

“Hello all.”

Just then, particles of light gathered in the corner of the room, and the high-class spirit Dryas manifested out of nowhere.

“Oh, Lady Dryas.”

“I sensed Aishia’s presence so I came to see her. You must be Celia. Sara and the others told us you’d be coming to the village. I’m Dryas,” she said, explaining her reasoning for appearing before them.

“You’re a humanoid spirit like Aishia... It’s nice to meet you. I’m Celia Claire. I’ve also heard about you from Rio and the others.”

“Yes, it’s a pleasure to meet you.”

“Mine as well.”

After they exchanged greetings...

“Hmm...”

Dryas stared closely at Celia from head to toe.

“Umm... Is something the matter?” Celia asked, blinking.

“You have a high affinity towards mana for a human. You excel at the manipulation of ode, don’t you?”

“Do... Do I?”

“Yes, mana naturally gathers near your body. Consequently, the ode flowing out of you has a very beautiful wavelength. Rio’s is on a different scale, but you’re not bad yourself. On the same level as the high elf Orphia, or thereabouts. You’re almost like an elf—do you have any ancestors who were elves? Perhaps it’s hereditary.”

“How can you tell that?”

“I haven’t been a humanoid spirit for hundreds of years for nothing. Aishia would be able to tell you the same. Spirits can visually see mana as well as ode.”

“I see...” Celia swallowed her breath, impressed by the knowledge of a high-class spirit that had existed for so long. Aishia was on the same level of existence as Dryas and was unmatched in combat strength, but her quiet personality and lack of spirit-like speech made it hard to think of her as a high-class spirit.

“Now that Lady Dryas and the elders have been introduced to Celia, I’d like to speak to Gouki’s group...” Rio began to say, looking at Gouki’s party seated in a corner of the room. The group included his wife Kayoko, daughter Komomo, Sayo, Shin, and others, totaling ten people. There were familiar faces among them, so there was no doubt they all hailed from the Karasuki Kingdom.

“Indeed. Where should we start...” Ursula stroked her chin in contemplation.

“Have you all heard about how Gouki is connected to my parents already?”

“Yes. Though I must apologize for talking about you in your absence.”

“Not at all, I’m sure it was unavoidable in order for you to understand each other. That being said, there must be unfamiliar faces on each side and unclear parts of the situation, so how about I introduce you first?”

“Good point. That would be preferred.”

“First, these are the close acquaintances of my parents, Gouki and his wife Kayoko, and their daughter Komomo. Gouki is a senior warrior of the Karasuki Kingdom, which is located in the Yagumo region... The equivalent to the head of the highest military noble house in the Strahl region. The people around him are most likely his retainers. Those two over there are villagers from my father’s hometown: Shin and his little sister Sayo. Though I’m not sure why they’re here...”

Rio conducted his introduction of Gouki’s party to Celia and the others, gesturing at them with his hand. They each bowed in the order of their names being called out, so it was fairly clear who was who.

“My name is Saga Gouki. Ah, but names in the Strahl region are the other way around, so it’d be Gouki Saga. This is my wife Kayoko, and we both served Sir Rio’s mother, Lady Ayame, together with his father Zen. That was over twenty years ago.”

With a ramrod straight back, Gouki introduced himself and his wife to Celia and Miharu, who were seated beside Rio.

“I just introduced them to the elders, but this is my former teacher Celia Claire, my adopted little sister Latifa, and Miharu Ayase, whom I live with. And this is my contract spirit, Aishia. You’ve met Sara’s group before, I believe,” Rio said to Gouki’s group.

They stared at the girls in great interest. Miharu in particular had similar black hair to what would be seen in the Yagumo region, and her name also sounded like theirs, so she attracted more attention than the rest.

Gouki nodded. “Yes, we spoke to Lady Sara and her friends three weeks ago.”

“I was told there was someone who wanted to see me at the village, but that must have been you and your people.”

The surprise from the sudden reunion had faded, but Rio still looked a little troubled.

“Yes. I’m sure it came as a surprise to you, but we wanted to speak to you directly. Please forgive my insolence in following you without permission.” Gouki bowed his head low enough to touch the floor.

“I don’t consider it insolence at all. I’m just bewildered... I didn’t expect you to chase after me,” Rio confessed with a somewhat exasperated sigh. He could tell they hadn’t pursued him with superficial feelings, so he couldn’t get mad at them.

“You said you could return to Strahl alone so you didn’t need retainers, and refused us clearly. We also said we’d give up on accompanying you.”

“You said you’d give up on accompanying me, but you didn’t say anything about not coming after me. Is that it?”

“Well, basically.” Gouki looked a little guilty but grinned widely. Rio sighed once again at his energy and initiative.

“The journey to this village couldn’t have been easy by any means.”

Savage creatures were rampant, and there was no road to follow. There were harrowing natural disasters local to certain areas, and some places were enshrouded in darkness all year round due to abnormal weather, making it impossible to ascertain the direction of travel. Just making it to the village would have been a harsh trip.

“It was beyond our expectations, but we were prepared for it. We knew it’d be an ordeal, and it was a good training experience in the end. We were fortunate to make it without losing anyone.”

“As long as there were no casualties.” Rio let out a breath of relief.

“Well, we restricted our companions to those who could use spirit arts. My retainers are all trained in that area, and while they still lack experience, Shin and Sayo gave it their best as well,” Gouki said, looking at the siblings.

“I really didn’t expect you to bring the two of them.”

Rio looked at them a little awkwardly. Why are they here? That was the question in his head, but he felt too awkward to ask it out loud.

“...” Sayo looked like she didn’t know what to do with herself and kept her head down in shame. Shin seemed displeased by that and had his lips fixed into a frown.

“Sayo had rather strong feelings for Sir Rio, you see... When I spoke to her, she asked to come along with me, so I agreed. Shin is also a man with lots of promise, and he cares deeply for his little sister under that rough attitude of his. He asked to come along for Sayo’s sake. The two of them came all the way here without a single complaint.”

Gouki looked at the silent siblings and sighed lightly, scratching his cheek before speaking on their behalf.

“Hmph.” Shin snorted unhappily. He’d been brusque since back in the village, but now he was especially biting.

“Hey now, Shin. What are you sulking for?”

“I’m not sulking.” Shin denied Gouki’s criticism with a grim look.

“Goodness. Sorry about that, Sir Rio.”

“No, there’s nothing to apologize for... Did Yuba and Ruri agree to them coming?”

“Of course. They’re accompanying us with full permission.”

“I see. In that case, can I ask for the details on how you all made it to this village?” Rio asked.

“We made it to the village by complete coincidence. We left the Karasuki Kingdom merely days after you, but we only arrived at this village about a month ago...”

“Lord Gouki and his people wandered into our forest after Rio took Sara and the girls to the Strahl region. When we listened to their situation, we found they were headed the same way—and then Rio’s name came up. We couldn’t just chase them out after that,” Ursula explained.

“The three elders told us that it wouldn’t be long before Sir Rio returned to this land, so they invited us to stay as guests. We’re extremely grateful to this village,” Gouki added.

“I understand now, I think. That means it’s my turn to give my report next.” There was a somber light in Rio’s eyes.

Sensing the state of his mind, Gouki put on a serious expression and refrained from conveying any praise or celebration. “Sara told us the general gist of things. You were able to achieve your long-held desire. I have no words to express myself.” He bowed his head to express his deep respect for Rio.

“I suppose it’d be weird for me to thank you... And I’m not sure what to say to your people after you went through such efforts to get here.”

Gouki looked confused at Rio’s uneasiness. “What do you mean?”

“With Lucius dead, there’s no reason for all of you to come to Strahl anymore, no?”

In other words, all their turmoil was for nothing.

“...Ha! Ha ha ha! What are you saying?” Gouki burst into hearty laughter after a pause.

“...” Rio was baffled by what could be so funny about his words.

“Ah, my apologies for making a ruckus. With all due respect, Sir Rio, you’ve misunderstood something. Vengeance on Lucius, the man who killed Lady Ayame and Zen... While that was indeed one of our goals, it wasn’t the only one,” Gouki said with a tense expression.

“By which you mean...?”

“Our goal is to serve you. Lucius’s death is positive news, and not a reason to feel disappointment. Our efforts will only end in vain when we become unable to swear our loyalty to you.”

“To serve me... When you didn’t even know if I’d agree to it? I’ve already refused your accompaniment once in the Yagumo region, so I’m sure you could imagine me refusing you again... And there was no guarantee you’d find me just by coming to Strahl.”

Yet Gouki and the others came after him. Rio felt an indescribable emotion at that fact, which showed on his utterly bewildered face.

“None of those serve as reasons not to come after you. We may be able to serve you. That possibility alone is enough—that is why we came after you.”

“To the extent of throwing away the land you were born and raised on? Your servants in particular never even served my mother. Have they truly assented to this?”

Friends, family, finances, status. They would be discarding all of those things by doing this. Going on such a dangerous journey for a wish that may not come true—wasn’t that a rather rash decision? Rio looked at them as though to say just that.

“Hmm, how should I put this...” Gouki struggled to find the right words.

“Sir Rio. My apologies for speaking up as a servant, but would you allow me to make one statement? I would like to explain the emotions of the servants on behalf of Sir Gouki.” Aoi, who was seated beside Komomo, raised her hand to ask for permission to speak.

“Of course, I don’t mind...” Rio looked at Aoi.

“Thank you very much. With the exception of Shin and Sayo, all the servants here are orphans adopted by the Saga family. We were given warm meals, clothes, shelter, and a means of living. Thus, we owe a great debt to Sir Gouki and Lady Kayoko. We will follow them wherever they go, and we will serve who they deem their master. That is our source of happiness.” Aoi bowed her head deeply as she explained their thoughts.

“I see...” Rio said, barely managing a reply.

He wasn’t born or raised as nobility, so it was difficult for him to put himself in their shoes. But that didn’t mean he couldn’t imagine it—he found their loyalty so admirable, he was almost astonished.

“We told the servants they could stay back with Hayate... But they all chose not to. Their loyalty is admirable, if I do say so myself,” Gouki said with a slightly bashful grin. He then looked at Rio with a heated gaze and declared, “However, both my wife and I pride ourselves in having loyalty for Sir Rio that won’t lose to theirs.”

“Why would you go so far for me? Sure, my father was your colleague and my mother was the master you served, but...” Rio was confused. He could tell that Gouki and Kayoko were extremely loyal to him, but he didn’t know the reason why. Was being Ayame’s son that important?

“Kayoko and I were unable to fulfill our vow of loyalty to Lady Ayame in the past. So we thought we could direct that lost loyalty towards her son instead. But our feelings cannot be expressed with that alone.” Gouki grinned shyly, rubbing at his neck in an embarrassed manner. The gesture made him seem embarrassed of his words.

“Lady Ayame and Zen were pursued by the kingdom and had to discard their identities, fleeing to the faraway lands of Strahl. We never thought we’d see them again, but one day their son shows up, bearing full resemblance to the two of them. That was the first time we saw Sir Rio,” Gouki said happily after a pause.

“That brings back memories. It was around two years ago, if I recall.” Rio also thought back on that moment with a distant look.

“I remember it as though it happened yesterday.”

“Ha ha ha.” Rio chuckled with nostalgia at Gouki’s proud statement.

“After listening to his words, we found out that both Zen and Lady Ayame have passed from this world. That Sir Rio made his way to the Karasuki Kingdom knowing nothing more than the stories Lady Ayame told him in his childhood. That he wanted to construct graves for them. He had made such a dangerous journey to the Yagumo region just to do that. Going around countless kingdoms to locate someone who knew of his parents... It must have been a hopeless journey with no end in sight. When we learned of this, we didn’t know what to feel...”

Gouki’s words were brimming with emotion. Rio looked a little uncomfortable, but everyone else was listening with serious faces. They were living vicariously through Gouki’s words, wondering how the clueless Rio appeared to him when he knew the truth of Ayame and Zen’s past.

“You were a dazzling existence to me. You were raised so well despite the harsh circumstances... I could only surrender to what a splendid person you ended up as.”

In other words, Gouki had felt extreme empathy for Rio at the time. He believed Rio was a person worth respect even without considering Ayame and Zen. As a military man and as a warrior, he fell for Rio as a person. He had been filled with joy when he received the letter from Yuba about Rio, but he hadn’t thought of swearing his loyalty yet. The more he got to know Rio, however, the more his resolution solidified.

“Of course, the fact that you’re a memento from Lady Ayame and Zen plays a big part, but it’s all because it’s you. We want to serve you because of the person you are—if we remained in Yagumo without swearing our loyalty, we would be living the rest of our lives in vain. That was something we were sure of. So how could we sit around waiting just because we were rejected once?”

Gouki gradually got more heated the more he spoke, but he seemed to realize that himself and paused. “At any rate, that’s the reason why we left the kingdom and came after you. Did that explain things clearly?” he asked shyly as he looked at Rio.

“...Yes.” Rio nodded after an awkward pause.

“In that case, I’d like to ask you once more: will you allow us the honor of swearing our loyalty to you?”

Gouki got out of his seat and proceeded to kneel on the floor before Rio. Kayoko, Komomo, and the other servants followed his lead quietly. The room focused on Rio for his response.

Even asking for favors made him feel awkward. Rio hesitated for a long moment before expressing his disapproval. “Honestly speaking, I’m not used to having someone swear loyalty to me. I doubt I’ll get used to it in the future, and I don’t think I can act like a master to you all. I’m not good at giving other people orders either.”

“I can imagine. I am well aware of your personality.”

Gouki seemed to have predicted such a response and had a strained smile on his face. However, he fixed his heated gaze on Rio to convey his desire to serve in spite of this.

“I understand everyone’s feelings. That’s why I won’t ask that you return to the Karasuki Kingdom. I’m at a loss.”

True to his words, Rio’s mouth was drawn into a completely stumped frown.

“Then...?”

Does that mean you’ll approve of us becoming your retainers? Gouki seemed to sense the possibility of that happening and looked at Rio in surprise.

He had imagined Rio would have answered based on the conclusion that he wouldn’t take Gouki and the others on as servants. No matter how difficult it was to reject them, the former Rio would have done so firmly, as he had done when he refused their accompaniment the first time.

So what about now? While he expressed his disapproval, he hadn’t given a clear no. Far from it, in fact.

“I cannot answer you right now... Could you give me some time to think about it?”

“O-Of course! Take all the time you need!” Gouki was unable to hold back his elated feelings and shouted his response. That was only understandable—for someone who wished to become one of Rio’s retainers, it was a great step forward. He hadn’t planned on giving up easily at a rejection, but this was a welcome miscalculation for someone who had prepared for a much longer battle.

Has accomplishing his long desire changed something within Sir Rio’s heart? Or perhaps it was the influence of these girls around him...

Gouki turned his gaze to Miharu, Celia, and the other girls around Rio. If there was something that had changed during his time away from Rio—other than the vengeance being achieved—it would be the presence of these girls. The elders seemed to have made the same assumption, believing Rio would refuse, as their eyes were widened as well.

“So please stand up for now,” Rio asked, trying to lighten the mood and relaxing his shoulders.

“This calls for a reunion banquet tonight!” Dominic suggested with a hearty laugh.

“You just want to drink, don’t you?” Ursula shrugged in exasperation.

“That aside, I’m sure there’s more you wish to discuss. Many of you are meeting for the first time, so it would be a good chance to interact with each other more.” Syldora summed up the discussions with a smile.

“Indeed. Whether you have an answer by the banquet or not, give it some thought, Rio.”

Rio nodded slowly at Ursula’s suggestion. “I will.”

“In that case, we shall excuse ourselves until the banquet. There’s no rush for a reply, so please give it as much thought as you need.”

Gouki offered for his people to make themselves scarce until they met up again at night.

◇　◇　◇

Leaving the elders in the town hall behind him, Rio headed for the guest house he had used when he previously stayed in the village. Komomo looked like she wanted to come with him but ended up going her separate way until the later banquet. This left Miharu, Celia, Aishia, Latifa, Sara, Orphia, and Alma to accompany Rio.

“This is the house we stay at while in the village,” Rio explained to Celia at the front door, inviting her inside.

“Whenever Onii-chan’s at the village, we all live together!” Latifa boasted smugly to Celia.

“Is this what you call a tree house? It’s so spacious on the inside... What a lovely home. I was thinking this as we walked earlier, but the people of this village really live in harmony with nature.”

Naturally, the wood of the host tree was being used as is, creating a space filled with a wooden warmth. It was a type of building that couldn’t be seen in Strahl cities, so Celia looked around the interior with great interest.

“Thank you very much. Please think of this place as your own while you’re here,” Sara said proudly as a resident of the village.

“The bathing room in this house is also quite delightful, so try it out at night,” Orphia noted.

“We’ll have to show you around the village too,” Alma added.

“Yup, I’m looking forward to it!” Celia nodded enthusiastically.

“It’d be nice if we could bring Aki and Masato here again someday. Right, Miharu?” Aishia said to Miharu out of consideration.

“Yeah.” Miharu nodded with a bright smile, though there was a faint trace of sadness to it.

Just then, Rio turned to everyone. “How about we take this chance to go for a walk around the village?”

The girls all exchanged looks. After hearing the conversation between Gouki and Rio earlier, they seemed to have their own thoughts about it. They tried to convey those thoughts to each other with just their eyes.

“Is something the matter...?” Rio asked, noticing how the girls were all making eye contact with each other.

“Onii-chan... If you need to talk, we’re here for you, yeah?”

As his adopted little sister, Latifa spoke on behalf of the girls. The rest of the group silently nodded along, expressing their agreement.

“You’re referring to Gouki and the others, right?” Rio smiled a little awkwardly on the receiving end of the girls’ gazes.

“Yeah.”

“I know the general direction I want to take... I’m just unsure of how to do it in a way that will make everyone happy, so I haven’t gathered my thoughts yet. Right. Would you be willing to hear me out? Everyone else too.”

“Of course!” The girls all agreed to Rio’s humble request in unison.

“Let’s sit on the chairs, then. I’ll take out the tea I prepared from the Time-Space Cache earlier.”

“I’ll help, Orphia.”

Orphia and Miharu headed towards the living room first. Rio and the others followed after them. Preparations were completed in a mere ten-odd seconds, and everyone sat down. The girls then naturally waited for Rio to start speaking, and after a while...

“Like I said earlier, I’m not capable of becoming a master to anyone. If they swear loyalty to me as retainers, I wouldn’t know how to interact with them as their master. That’s why I’m opposed to the idea of taking them on...” Rio began.

“But when I look at you now, I can see you want to answer Gouki and his people’s feelings. That’s why you’re wavering, isn’t it?” Celia said, watching Rio’s expression as though to seek confirmation.

Rio confirmed her statement with a strained smile. “Well, yes.”

“Does that mean you intend on taking Gouki’s group on as retainers?” Sara asked next.

“No... I don’t want retainers, but I’d be willing to live with them on equal footing like with everyone here... Gouki and the others are all important people to me, just like you all.”

He had no confidence in his ability to act as a master, so he was opposed to making Gouki his retainer. But if they insisted on staying with him anyway, he wanted to grant their wishes. The solution he came up with was for them to be comrades.

“I see...” The girls seemed to be thoroughly convinced by that.

“Why don’t you tell them that, then?” Miharu suggested while watching Rio’s expression.

“Yes, I agree,” was Celia’s endorsement. The others also uttered their agreement.

Rio scratched his cheek, unsure. “I’m not sure Gouki will accept that...”

“Why? I don’t see why not...” Celia looked surprised.

“If Gouki’s people are fixated on becoming retainers, they might find my proposal disappointing...”

I can’t make you my retainers, but do you want to come along? Was that the reply Gouki and the others truly desired? Rio couldn’t help but ponder that.

“I believe you’re giving it too much thought...” Sara said with a wry smile.

Celia agreed tiredly. “Right. It’s a bad habit of yours.”

“Have more confidence, Onii-chan! It’ll definitely go well!”

Latifa pumped her fist to cheer Rio on. Rio looked a little embarrassed at that.

“If Gouki and his people join me, they’ll naturally end up interacting with you more... Are you all okay with that?” he asked, changing the subject subtly.

“Yup. They seem like really nice people, so I’m looking forward to talking to them at the banquet tonight,” Latifa replied with great curiosity.

Miharu giggled in agreement. “That’s right.”

“Then it won’t be a problem if they end up living together with us.”

“No. All that’s left is for you to tell them how you feel.”

“Ah ha ha... Right.” Rio chuckled weakly and nodded.

“Say, Rio... A master-servant relationship can come in all shapes and forms. You may not think you’re capable of standing above others, but I don’t agree. That’s probably why Gouki and the others want to serve you as well—like Latifa said, have more confidence. Right?” Celia smiled with a one-sided dimple as she gave her opinion from the point of view of a noble. That made Rio’s expression brighten as well.

“Right.” He nodded.

“Hmph. As expected of Celia. You weren’t Onii-chan’s teacher for nothing.” Latifa’s cheeks puffed up like a balloon. Other than Aishia, the other girls all looked similarly envious.

“N-No no, I didn’t say anything special,” Celia said, flustered.

“Well, that aside... There’s one thing I wanted to ask Onii-chan before the banquet.”

“What is it?” Rio met Latifa’s eyes and stiffened in wariness.

“Umm, you know. We might end up living together with them from now on, so we need to know more about them, don’t you think?”

“Uh, I guess...”

There was nothing wrong with what she was saying, but for some reason, Rio had a bad feeling about it as he agreed with her.

“Then, a question! What happened with that Sayo girl? And that Komomo girl too.” Latifa’s hand immediately shot up in the air as she fired off her questions.

“U-Umm...?” Rio was flustered by the sudden interrogation.

“Based on Sayo’s reaction, something definitely happened between you two at the Karasuki village, didn’t it?”

“Uh... I wonder about that...” Rio tried to feign ignorance, but—

“That’s a lie! That’s definitely a lie! Right, girls?!” Latifa sought agreement from Miharu and the others.

“Indeed.”

Everyone nodded in agreement. Celia had been avoiding the prying questioning, but she took the chance to nod along with them. Thus, an encircling net of questions was laid around Rio within moments.

“I-It’s a private matter.” Rio averted his eyes guiltily.

“See! Something happened! That answer means something happened!” Latifa glared at Rio.

“Spare me...” Rio groaned, at a complete loss. Thus, the time before the banquet was filled with a barrage of questions from the girls.

◇　◇　◇

Finally, the banquet was upon them, and it was to take place in the large dining room in the village town hall.

“Listen up, everyone! There’ll be no stiff greetings tonight. We drink, and we talk! Cheers!” Dominic raised his glass with enough momentum to splash the ceiling. Of course, he wasn’t tall enough to actually reach the ceiling...

“Cheers!”

Glasses were raised across the room, accompanied by cheering voices. Rio also raised his glass and tapped it against Miharu’s, Celia’s, Aishia’s, Latifa’s, Sara’s, Orphia’s, and Alma’s.

“Cheers, everyone!” Dryas skipped over and clinked her glass against them all one by one.

“Latifa! Rio! Sara...and everyone else!”

“Ah, it’s Vera and Arslan!”

Latifa’s close friend—and Sara’s little sister—Vera came up to them, waving her hands enthusiastically. Behind her was the lion werebeast, Arslan, and the chief warrior of the village, Uzuma.

“Long time no see, everyone!” Vera’s silver wolf tail wagged happily as she greeted them.

“It’s been so long, Vera!”

“Yes! I’ve missed you so much!”

The two girls hugged each other, rejoicing in their reunion. Arslan shot them an exasperated look before turning to Rio.

“Hey, Rio.”

“It’s good to see you again, Arslan. And you too, Uzuma.”

“Yes, I’m glad to see you in good health, Lord Rio.”

“You too, Uzuma. Although Aki and Masato stayed behind in Strahl...” Rio said.

“We heard about that last time Sara and the others returned. Masato still owes me that sparring match. Ugh...” Arslan muttered, disappointed.

“Masato wanted to see you too, Arslan. It might take some time, but I’ll figure out a way to bring them here again someday.”

“Please do.”

“Leave it to me.” Rio nodded. He then looked over at Gouki and the others from Yagumo, who were waiting a few meters away. “Hold on, I’m going to say hello to Gouki.”

He started walking, but—

“Ah, we’ll come too.”

The others who were listening to the conversation followed behind him.

“Will you allow me to make a toast to you all?” Rio checked over his shoulder for the people following him, then started talking to the group by raising his glass.

“Of course!” Gouki replied with delight, having been waiting for Rio to approach them.

“Cheers.”

Rio and Gouki tapped their glasses together as the others present raised theirs.

Gouki gulped down the contents of his drink and started chatting merrily. “This is such a nice banquet, isn’t it? I enjoy a good banquet wherever I go. And the alcohol in this village is superb! I was surprised to see they had Yagumo drinks as well.”

“The dwarves probably made it. There’s no one in this village who appreciates a good drink more than them.”

“So it seems! I have confidence in my ability to hold a drink, so I was shocked when the high-ranking dwarves of this village all turned out to be heavy drinkers.”

“It sounds like you adapted to the village well.”

“Only thanks to you, Sir Rio. Things were really tense until your name came up.”

“This village has always been extremely hesitant about accepting humans... But how did my name come up?”

“We figured if we came across this village on our way to Strahl, then there was a chance you did as well. There was no guarantee, but I believed it was possible you stopped on your way and asked them.”

And it was worth the attempt.

“I see.”

“This village is full of experienced warriors, including Lady Uzuma over there. With the disadvantage in location and numbers, there’s no doubt we would have been captured if we responded wrongly.” Gouki laughed heartily with a glance at Uzuma. “That aside, I want to hear your tales too, Sir Rio. Komomo and Sayo have been wanting to speak as well. May they join in?”

The two girls had been restlessly listening to the conversation beside them, so Gouki glanced over and sought permission from Rio to include them.

“Sure. And I’d prefer it if you didn’t worry about formalities like that, truly. It’s in the past, so please forget my mother’s status,” Rio requested with a frown.

“That’s a rather difficult request... But I understand. You heard him, come join the convo. There’ll be no standing on ceremony tonight.” Gouki beckoned them over.

“My little sister and my friends have been wanting to talk to the three of you as well,” Rio said, looking at Latifa and the others behind him.

“Oh, what an honor. I previously heard that you have an adopted sister, so it’s a pleasure to finally meet Lady Latifa in person. As mentioned earlier, I am Gouki Saga, former guard to Rio’s late mother, Lady Ayame.” Gouki bowed his head low before Latifa, extending his deep loyalty to her as well.

Latifa stiffened at the strong display of respect towards her, then bobbed her head with a polite curtsy. “Ah ha ha... I’m not related by blood to Onii-chan’s mom or dad, so there’s no need to be so formal. My name’s Latifa. It’s nice to meet you.”

“Blood connections are irrelevant when it comes to Sir Rio’s little sister. May I ask how old you are? At a glance, you seem to be the same age as Komomo...”

“Umm, I’m thirteen.”

“I see. That makes you one year older than Komomo.” Gouki glanced at his daughter.

“Wow, really? Let’s get to know each other, Komomo!”

“Yes, Lady Latifa.” Komomo gave a cute smile and energetic reply to Latifa’s greeting.

“There’s no need to call me that. I don’t want to be called a ‘lady’ by someone my age, and we’re only one year apart... Right? There’s no need for titles.” Latifa looked embarrassed.

Komomo hesitantly looked between Gouki and Rio. “But you are Sir Rio’s sister...”

“I want to become friends with you... Do you not want to be friends?” Latifa cocked her head uneasily, watching Komomo’s expression. Social status and position were barriers to forming friendships. For the daughter of an established warrior who was trained in etiquette, social standing was an important matter. It was a difficult issue to address, but...

“I would like to ask the same of you, Komomo,” Rio requested.

“Umm...” Komomo was in clear conflict with herself.

“The people in question are saying this themselves. It wouldn’t hurt to agree to a friendship in this case.” Gouki smiled gently and gave his permission. He felt a slight objection himself, but he was capable of considering the circumstances and adapting to them.

Komomo took a long, deep breath and said Latifa’s name nervously. “Then... Latifa...?”

“Yup! Please be good to me, Komomo!”

“...Of course!”

The two exchanged friendly smiles.

“Let me introduce my friends to you next! Do you know them already? This is Vera, and beside her is Arslan.” Latifa pulled Komomo by the hand and led her over to where Vera and Arslan were behind Miharu and Sara’s group. Thus, the younger ones began mingling with each other.

“U-Uh, I think you’ve got the completely wrong idea here,” Rio finally realized.

“What’s with all of them being so cute, anyway? Rio, were you always such a sucker for pretty faces? And is Sayo okay with this?!” Ruri seemed to have been quite shocked by this news, as she continued on down the road of her misunderstood thinking.

“W-Wait, Ruri! You’ve definitely misunderstood something! I’ll introduce them properly, so calm down.”

“M-Misunderstood? What have I misunderstood here?”

Rio had grabbed Ruri by the shoulders in a fluster, attempting to correct her mistake. Meanwhile, the other girls saw his speech take on a more natural tone than usual.

“Onii-chan seems really close to Ruri,” Latifa commented, as though she were seeing something rare.

“Yes. He’s talking to her like he does with you and Aishia, on very familiar terms. He looks like he’s enjoying himself.”

Celia spoke with a pleasant smile, but she seemed somewhat saddened and envious at the same time. On one hand, she was glad she could see a side of Rio she didn’t know, but on the other, she felt conflicted that it wasn’t directed towards her. She yearned to be the one who could bring out such rare expressions on his face.

The same seemed to apply to the others too; everyone had a similar look on their faces. Meanwhile, the villagers watching the girls were able to guess at their relationship to Rio by those expressions.

The boys grit their teeth while looking at Rio, then glanced at Shin to question him. Shin nodded in confirmation.

“Oh, now I remember. Back when this guy was in the village...”

The young men recalled the hardships from when all the young girls were in love with Rio. They glared at him as if to curse him with their gazes.

“I’ve told you about how I have an adopted little sister, right? And my teacher whom I owe a lot to as well. The others started living with me due to various circumstances, so I came back to the village to introduce them all to everyone...” Rio explained, looking over at Celia and Latifa to beckon them closer. But when he realized the village boys were glaring at him, he closed his mouth in hesitation to call them over.

“H-Huh, really?” Ruri looked at Latifa and Celia happily. However...

“Hey, Rio!”

“Are you seriously living with all these cute girls?!”

“You’ve gotta be kidding me!”

“Why is it always you?!”

“That’s right, it’s unfair! Introduce them to us already!”

The boys closed in on Rio with their protests.

“I’ll introduce them to everyone, so just wait. Hold on a moment!” Rio tried to stop them with his hands, but it was a futile attempt.

“Good, go get him.” Shin cheered his friends on while Sayo scolded him in a fluster.

“Don’t spur them on, Shin!”

“It’s fine. This is the last step of acceptance towards Rio,” Shin said knowingly. In reality, the boys had teasing smiles on their faces, so it was clear they were just messing around. Like Shin said, this was their way of welcoming Rio back to the village.

“R-Ruri, save me...” Rio said, seeking some kind of safety net.

“You know I can’t stop them once they get like this. Sorry! I’ll show everyone the way to Gran’s place, so catch up to us once you’re free, Rio!”

Ruri seemed to be enjoying the situation, as she spoke with a cheery voice. She clapped her hands together and bowed her head at Rio. Then, she approached Miharu and the others and called out to them in a friendly manner.

“Hi, everyone. I’ll show you the way to my place, so follow me. Come on!”

“Umm... But...”

Miharu and the girls looked at Rio hesitantly, wondering if it was all right to leave him behind. Rio was sandwiched between the boys of the village and was being shaken violently for answers to their questions.

“It’s fine, it’s fine. It happened frequently back when he was in the village. And keep up, Sayo.” Stifling a giggle, Ruri encouraged the girls to get moving.

“Hmph. We’re going as well, Sayo.” Shin huffed triumphantly and pushed Sayo along.

“Hmm... It’d be tactless to stop the villagers from conducting their welcome. It’s not like anyone’s getting hurt either. Let us go as well.”

It would be easy for Rio to slip out of that circle if he wanted to. The fact he didn’t meant he wasn’t as unhappy about it as one would think. With that thought, Gouki, Kayoko, and their servant Aoi followed after Ruri as well.

By the time Rio was finally freed, the others were completely out of sight.

◇　◇　◇

After that, Miharu and the others were shown to the village chief Yuba’s home by Ruri. They had just arrived at the house when Rio caught up to them and they entered the house together.

Yuba was just as surprised as the other villagers by the unexpected guests, but when she spotted Rio and Gouki among them, she was even more surprised. But she soon regained her composure and exchanged reunion greetings with Rio and Gouki, then listened to a summary of what had happened since they arrived in the village.

“Ah ha ha, that was unfortunate.”

Yuba cackled when she heard Rio had been crushed by the village boys.

“Wow, Granny’s in a good mood,” Ruri mumbled, guessing it was because Rio had returned.

“That aside... You’ve brought a rather large group with you.” Yuba looked around at the faces of the girls Rio had brought, humming in wonder. The girls all seemed to be nervous, as they were kneeling on the floor stiffly.

“And they’re all beauties to boot. No wonder the younger villagers were making a fuss.”

“Right? I was surprised too.” Ruri nodded her agreement to Yuba’s stifled laughter.

“Well? Hurry and introduce them,” Yuba pressed.

“Well, starting with the two I mentioned while I was staying here... This is my former teacher Celia and adopted little sister Latifa,” Rio said while gesturing with his hands.

“Oho.”

“Next to Latifa, starting from the right are Sara, Orphia, and Alma. The three are from the same village, and they always give me a helping hand on a daily basis,” he then said, introducing the three from the spirit folk village.

“Then there’s Miharu and Aishia, who started living together with me after various circumstances. The seven of them are as important as family to me,” he said, scratching at his cheek shyly while explaining their relationship to him.

“In other words...they’re people you’re dating with the intention of marriage?”

“N-No, that’s not what I meant...” Rio ducked his head in embarrassment.

“Hee hee, I’m just joking. It seems like you were able to meet some good girls. You have a much better expression on your face... It reminds me of Zen when he snuck Lady Ayame out to visit the village,” Yuba said, teasing Rio with a gentle look in her eyes and a smile.

“Ha ha ha, it was quite the ordeal back then.”

Gouki and Kayoko also smiled at their fond memories of those times, their emotions showing keenly on their faces.

“Everyone. I’ve never been able to do anything grandmother-like for Rio, but thank you for treating him well.”

There was no sign of Yuba’s usual to-the-point way of speaking as she bowed her head at the girls courteously.

“N-No, we should be saying that!” Miharu, Celia, and Sara lowered their heads in a fluster.

“Rio’s the one always taking care of us.”

Orphia and Alma returned the bow. Aishia imitated the others; the usually taciturn girl had a gentle smile on her face.

Meanwhile, Latifa was still being shy in front of someone she didn’t know, bowing meekly along with everyone in silence.

“Hey, I’m really curious about each and every one of you, but...if Latifa is Rio’s adopted sister, then that makes you my cousin as well, right?” Ruri asked.

“It would also make her my granddaughter,” Yuba added.

“Huh? Ah, yes... I’d be delighted if you thought of me that way.” Latifa nodded shyly, keeping her eyes downcast.

“Aww, how adorable. I’ve always wanted a little sister. It’s nice to meet you, Latifa... Can I just call you by your name like that? I mean, I’m already calling you that, but...”

“Of course. Can I just call you ‘Ruri’ as well? And...Granny Yuba...”

“Definitely! Please do!”

“Indeed.”

Ruri and Yuba agreed happily.

“Eh heh heh, thank you very much.”

“Aww! You’re so cute! Let’s talk a lot, okay?” Overcome with emotions at Latifa’s shyness, Ruri hugged her happily. She then turned to address the others. “And everyone else too!”

“So, how long will you be in the village, Rio? We’ll hold a welcome feast for you all tonight, but it looks like these girls could talk forever at this rate,” said Yuba.

“I’m thinking of heading to the capital in the near future with Gouki’s family, but could Latifa and the others stay in the village during that time? I’m afraid there are too many people to take on an unannounced visit...”

“Naturally.” Yuba nodded warmly.

“Thank you very much. I believe I’ll be back after a two-week stay there, so please look after them for that time.”

“This is your home as well. There’s no need to be so reserved.”

“Right...” Rio’s face crinkled in a shy smile.

“Then it’s decided. Shin, Sayo. While you two go and greet the other villagers, can you inform them there’s a feast tonight?”

“Yeah, sure.”

“Right away.”

At Yuba’s request, the siblings stood up.

“In that case, I’ll help with the cooking. I’ve brought plenty of ingredients and alcohol too,” Rio offered, causing Miharu and Orphia to promptly offer their assistance as well.

“Yay! We get to eat your cooking again,” Ruri cheered happily.

Thus, just like when they visited the spirit folk village, another welcome banquet was to be held.

◇　◇　◇

That evening...

It was still a little early to begin the feast, but eager villagers were already starting to gather at the central square.

Rio had finished cooking with everyone and was visiting the hill outside the village. His purpose was, of course, to pay his respects at his parents’ graves.

Surrounding Rio were the people he had arrived at the village with. Earlier, when he informed Gouki and Kayoko he was going to visit their graves, the others had expressed their wish to come too. Moving in such a large group attracted attention, but Ruri went with them and told the villagers they passed that she was giving them a quick tour before the feast. Thus, they arrived at the hill without anyone’s notice.

Rio was the first to slowly walk up to the stone monument. The others maintained a distance out of consideration for him. When Rio noticed their discretion, his mouth turned up in a faint smile as he proceeded forward.

This place hasn’t changed at all...

He looked around at the scenery from the hill. When he looked at the almost setting sun over the village, it felt like no time had passed since the last time he was here.

However, the boy from back then was different compared to who he was now. Something within his heart had definitely changed... Rio himself could feel that keenly.

Mom. Dad. I achieved my goal. I killed Lucius...

Would the two of them rejoice at knowing that? Perhaps they’d be saddened by it. The dead couldn’t talk, so there was no way for him to know the answer.

But that was fine. He hadn’t decided to pursue vengeance for someone else’s approval. He hadn’t achieved vengeance for someone else.

Two years ago, Rio had sworn vengeance on this hill for none other than himself.

That’s why if something had changed within Rio, it would be that the frozen clock within him had started moving once again. Perhaps not moving at the right speed, but it was slowly and certainly beginning to tick. However...

I probably wouldn’t be like this just by getting my revenge, though, Rio thought to himself. And the reason was because he himself hadn’t accepted it—the fact he had gotten his revenge, that is. He understood that revenge was an evil deed, and did it anyway... Rio would have continued hating himself like that.

However, he didn’t detest himself that much anymore. There were people who claimed they wanted to stay beside someone like him, so he was able to like himself a little. Though he still didn’t have much confidence...

I don’t want to lose the things important to me. That’s why I tried to let go of them. After I tried to do something so selfish, everyone extended their hands to me. That’s why it’s my turn to repay them.

On the hill he once swore vengeance at, Rio made a new decision in his heart. He pressed his hands together before the nameless graves of his parents as though to make a vow.

This secret grave was built in memory of the two people who would never return to the Karasuki Kingdom again by the few who were aware of the circumstances. As such, there were no corpses resting here. Not even Rio knew where their bodies were, but he nevertheless still treated this place as their graves, placing his hands together to mourn them.

After a moment, Rio lowered his hands and lifted his face, turning around to head back to the others.

“Thank you very much, everyone.” He beamed dazzlingly while facing the sunset, calling out to everyone with a soft voice.

After that, Gouki and Kayoko, Miharu and Celia, then Latifa and the others all took turns paying their respects to Rio’s parents. Then, they headed to the feast, where they received an enthusiastically warm welcome from the villagers and partied late into the night.

◇　◇　◇

Two days after arriving at the Karasuki Kingdom village, Rio was to head for the Karasuki capital with Gouki, Kayoko, Komomo, and Aoi. With Orphia’s assistance, that morning, they transported them all to the capital. They landed on a hill by the roadside at the outskirts of the city.

“We’ll meet back here in three days at noon.”

They made a promise to meet up and bid farewell to Orphia, who returned to the village.

Afterwards, the five of them entered the capital and headed for Gouki’s residence first. Part of the reason they didn’t go straight to the castle was so that Gouki and the others could visit their home again, but also because Gouki was currently retired and considered missing.

In order to secretly chase after Rio, he and his family had run off without notice. If they suddenly showed up at the castle now, they’d create a fuss and inevitably need to go through a number of formalities; it was a far better plan to catch up with Hayate and have him arrange a meeting with King Homura and Queen Shizuku in secret instead.

Hayate was shocked by the sudden return of his family, but as soon as he understood the circumstances, he set off into action. He returned before noon with an appointment arranged for the next afternoon.

Thus, Hayate brought them to the royal castle as quietly as possible. Rio was shown to the room where he had met the king and queen once before.

“Thank you for making time for me on the day of my sudden arrival, King Homura, Queen Shizuku.” Rio sat down on the seat opposite to his grandparents and bowed his head.

“You returned to us—of course I’d adjust our plans to prioritize this. Not to mention you were accompanied by Gouki and Kayoko, who went after you. I couldn’t have more important guests than this.” Homura looked truly happy to be seeing the memory of his daughter Ayame once again.

“Don’t you mean ‘we,’ not ‘I,’ dear?” Homura’s wife, Shizuku, puffed up her cheeks in a pout. Rio’s grandmother was nearly forty years apart in age from him, but her sulking face was awfully cute.

“Ha ha ha. Forgive me.” Homura laughed and apologized sincerely.

“I’m so glad we’re able to see you again, Rio. You did well returning alive. It’s so reassuring seeing you healthy.” Shizuku sighed in relief, a soft look in her eyes. Her expression was exactly the same as Ayame’s face in Rio’s memories.

“Many things have happened since I left Yagumo, but it was all thanks to other people.” Rio had a somewhat distant look in his eyes as he nodded with a gentle smile.

“Hayate has informed us of the general situation, but will you tell us the details yourself?” Homura asked.

“Yes. That’s what I came to do. I’ll start with what happened first.”

Rio summarized the events that happened from the moment he departed from Karasuki for revenge until his return to the castle now. He narrowed down the matters to only the minimum facts, completing his report in a matter of minutes. Finally, he ended with conveying his intent to travel together with Gouki’s family from now on.

“It seems you’ve been blessed with all kinds of meetings. Perhaps that’s why I thought you had a rather positive expression on your face when I first entered the room.” Homura stared at Rio’s face and smiled, pleased.

“Oh my, you too? I thought the same,” Shizuku agreed happily with her husband.

“Heh heh heh. Everyone who meets Sir Rio says the same thing. I actually thought the same myself,” Gouki said proudly.

“Is it that clearly written on my face?” Rio touched his cheeks with his hand, cocking his head curiously.

“Hmm... It’s not entirely gone, but it’s like the shadow over you has faded a lot. Perhaps it was the manifestation of your strong will...” Homura described the difference in Rio’s expression with tact—he wasn’t the ruler of a kingdom for nothing.

“Maybe it’s because my revenge is done?” Rio wondered shyly.

“Ha ha ha. Indeed, there are those who make bright faces after achieving their revenge. However, such people also tend to have hints of aggression in their expressions, as though putting their legitimacy on display. They don’t have hints of guilt in their expressions like you.”

Because they believed they were in the right, they had bright faces with no sign of guilt. That was Homura’s instant rebuttal—the accurate analysis of a king who had looked at many people before.

“If that’s how my face looks to King Homura right now, then it’s exactly as you say. I believe I was blessed with good meetings,” Rio agreed.

Shizuku looked as happy as if it had happened to her. “You must have wonderful people around you...”

“Yes... Those people stayed close to me, saying they wanted to be with me despite my decision to live for revenge. That’s what made me realize I had gained as many precious things as I had lost.” Rio smiled softly as he expressed the change in his heart.

“The truth is...when you first mentioned pursuing vengeance, I was worried you’d return an empty shell if you succeeded. However, I couldn’t advise you against doing it... But at any rate, it seemed to be a groundless fear.” Homura had a pained expression thinking of that past Rio but relaxed his tensed body at the end.

“I know this may just sound convenient, but now that I’ve accomplished what I set out to do, I want to live without losing what’s important to me.”

For the sake of myself, and most importantly, for the sake of everyone else... Rio’s expression tightened with his resolution.

“I understand. So that’s why you agreed to accept Gouki’s family.”

“Yes...”

“But what do you plan on doing now? Will you remain in Karasuki?”

Homura looked slightly nervous for some reason, watching Rio’s expression for any changes.

If... If he chooses to remain in the Karasuki Kingdom...

Perhaps they would be able to provide a quiet life for him, Homura thought, but...

“I’m thinking of returning to the Strahl region again,” Rio answered without hesitation.

“I see... Things will get lonely again, then.” Homura frowned in disappointment.

“I have to return to Strahl for the sake of those important to me. I’m sorry.”

There were Miharu’s, Satsuki’s, Aki’s, and Masato’s futures to consider... And there was Celia as well. In which case, he figured he had no choice but to settle in the Strahl region.

“It’s nothing to apologize for.”

“Thank you... However, while I will spend more time in Strahl, I’d like to increase the frequency of my visits here as well. If it isn’t a problem for you, will you allow me to visit you like this again?”

Rio was able to make the trip from Strahl to Yagumo and back in a month. Unless there was some emergency requiring his presence, he could arrange to visit periodically.

“Of course.”

“We’d never turn you away.”

Homura’s and Shizuku’s voices overlapped.

“Thank you very much...” Rio relaxed.

“We would’ve liked to meet the people who changed you and thank them ourselves...” Shizuku sighed in disappointment, being curious about them.

“I’m afraid I can’t bring them all to this castle. Their numbers would attract attention.”

It would be a little too suspicious if a crowd of strangers showed up at the castle to visit the king and queen. While the black-haired Miharu could pass for a Yagumo resident, Celia, Aishia, Latifa, Sara, Orphia, and Alma all had different facial features to those of the locals. Although the spirit folk girls currently had their racial traits concealed via artifacts and could similarly change their hair color if they wished, they’d still be suspected of being foreign.

“It’ll be difficult meeting them within the castle, but if it were outside of the castle...” Homura pondered with a hum. He then turned to Rio to ask, “Incidentally, how long do you intend on staying at Lady Yuba’s village for?”

“Around two weeks, I’d say...” Rio’s eyes widened at the implied possibility of meeting outside the castle. There were strict restrictions for when the king and queen could go out, but...

“If it’s for a very brief period of time, then it’s not impossible. We may need to ask Lady Orphia for her help, though...” Gouki grinned and looked at Rio.

“Is that the truth?” Homura asked.

“Tell us more, Gouki,” Shizuku added.

“It’s possible to conceal your whereabouts for a few hours, right? You just need to finish your rendezvous within that time. Isn’t that right, Sir Rio?” Gouki said with a wicked grin. With his knowledge of Ariel, that was enough for Rio to understand Gouki’s idea.

“I’m willing to give it a try, but is it okay for Your Majesties to sneak out of the castle?” Rio asked, considering the risks.

“We’ll cross that bridge when we get there. If it’s a matter of a few hours, I can make up a lie. If something does happen, I’ll take responsibility as the king. So, how do we slip out of the castle?”

Homura declared his resolve, eyes sparkling with regained youth. He must have really wanted to meet the people precious to Rio, as he was brimming with eagerness.

“Oh my, it reminds me of when Ayame used to sneak out of the castle to visit Zen’s village. I never thought I’d be able to do the same.” Shizuku was on board as well.

Thus, the operation for the secret visit pressed ahead under the leadership of the king and queen themselves. They arrived at the village three days later with Orphia’s help, surprising Yuba and everyone else.

Chapter 6: The Saint’s Attack

Two weeks had passed since Liselotte had her conversation with Saint Erica.

After visiting the spirit folk village and Karasuki Kingdom, Rio had returned to the Strahl region once more. However, the only ones with him were the group who originally set off with him—that is, Miharu, Celia, Aishia, Latifa, Sara, Orphia, and Alma. Gouki, Kayoko, Komomo, and the others were not present. Their family had over ten people, which was too many for Ariel to carry.

That was when the idea of teleporting to the Strahl region was brought up. It was a two-week journey by air, so transporting everyone was possible if they split into two groups, but the elders thankfully offered to arrange the production of a teleportation crystal.

Thus, Gouki’s group was temporarily staying in the spirit folk village. Rio and the others would go to the Galarc Kingdom first, set up a teleportation point, then inform Francois of Gouki’s presence before bringing them there from the spirit folk village.

And so, after arriving at the Galarc Kingdom, Rio went through the usual procedures to enter the castle and headed for his mansion.

“I’ll go and report our return. Everyone else, please stay here.”

Rio took only Miharu and Celia and left the mansion for the main castle. Of course, his report went to Satsuki, Charlotte, and King Francois directly.

Francois was busy with government affairs, so it wasn’t always possible to meet him right away, but Satsuki and Charlotte were probably available. He had asked for early notice to be sent while he was completing the entry procedure into the castle, so they might even be waiting for him at the castle entrance. Rio approached the front of the castle with such thoughts, when...

“Haruto! Miharu! Celia! Come quickly!”

It was Satsuki, but something was wrong. She was gesturing them over in a fret.

Rio and the others ran over. “What’s the matter...?”

“Just come. It’s terrible... There’s a hero, who’s also a saint, in the castle right now, having an audience with the king. Hurry!”

Satsuki started running, tugging them along.

“A hero, who’s also a saint? I understand if she wants an audience with the king, but...”

What’s the problem with that? Satsuki was in such a panic; her explanation didn’t make sense. Until...

“She’s abducted Liselotte!”

At those words, Rio’s expression instantly stiffened.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, in a meeting room reserved for high-ranking royalty in the castle...

“This discussion is getting nowhere.”

“I was just thinking the same.”

Saint Erica and King Francois of Galarc were currently engaged in conversation. They sat facing each other in chairs on either side of the door, sighing heavily at each other.

“We just want you to return Liselotte without aggravating matters. Is it that disagreeable for you?” Francois suggested.

“Why must I be forced to accept that when I’m the victim? Liselotte Cretia’s subordinate laid her hands on me first, okay?” Erica said, turning down the suggestion curtly. Aria was standing in a corner of the room, glaring furiously at her. Liselotte’s parents, Cedric and Julianne, were also present. Erica met eyes with Aria and smirked.

“However, Liselotte’s attendant has given a different account. According to Aria’s testimony, you tried to harm Liselotte first.”

“You doubt the words of a hero?” Erica asked arrogantly.

“I will believe the testimony that matches Liselotte’s own account, as she has my trust. That is why I’m asking you to return her.”

“Isn’t that the same as doubting my words? If I return her, you’ll be able to make up as many excuses as you want.”

“Even if that were true, I’ve already said I do not wish to aggravate things... In that case, bring Liselotte here and have her testify herself.”

“You want me to bring my hostage into enemy territory? That’s the same as saying to return her, is it not?”

“No, that’s not what I’m saying. You can just bring her here. I only wish to confirm that she’s safe.”

“If I brought her here, you’d just make up reasons to hide her. Are you trying to force me into giving up? I’d like to see the fool who would take you up on such an offer.”

“...” Francois sighed heavily.

It was at that moment that the door to the meeting room opened, and Satsuki appeared with Rio, Miharu, and Celia.

“Oh, your hero has returned as well,” Erica looked at Satsuki and said, “along with...a rather cute Japanese girl, I see. I’m Saint Erica, leader of the Holy Democratic Republic of Erica. It’s nice to meet you. Are you Satsuki’s friend?” Erica spotted Miharu and started talking to her in a friendly manner. However...

“You can ignore her, Miharu,” Satsuki whispered to Miharu in an irritated voice. Her voice should have been too quiet for Erica to hear.

“Why, so you’re called Miharu. Written as ‘beautiful spring,’ I assume? Or is it written as ‘three springs’? Just between you and me, my family name in Japan was written with the character for ‘cherry blossom.’ I think we could be good friends.”

“What? No way, how could she hear that...”

“I could tell by the movement of your lips. I’m good at things like that,” Erica revealed to Satsuki, who was shocked that she was overheard whispering Miharu’s name.

“She may seem friendly at a glance, but this person abducted Liselotte. She keeps on refusing to return her too.”

“Abduction? Don’t spread false rumors. I was assaulted, so I simply took her into custody as a hostage. I’m just a small nation up against a major kingdom, after all,” Erica added, sounding offended.

“Has there been any progress, Char?”

Satsuki brought Rio, Miharu, and Celia over to Charlotte, who shook her head sadly. “Unfortunately not.”

“How about you state your demands already, Hero Saint Erica? This loop of refusing to return her to us is getting nowhere,” Francois said, having reached the end of his patience.

“Oh, how could I forget? I have five directives to pass on to you. First, the abolition of the monarchy. Second, the abolition of the nobility system. Third, to transfer the country to the people. Fourth, to transfer Liselotte Cretia to the Holy Democratic Republic of Erica. Fifth, to transfer the Ricca Guild’s fortune and right of management to the Holy Democratic Republic of Erica.”

That is all. Erica ended with a sunny expression.

“Are you being serious right now? How could I accept any of those conditions?”

Making such demands of another kingdom was as good as declaring war on them. Even Francois frowned severely at that.

“I don’t expect you to accept them. However, I will make them happen. That’s why they’re not demands, but predetermined facts. It was hard to bring them up while you were trying to make negotiations, but I actually came here today to inform you of this. If you don’t fulfill the conditions that I have presented, I will make them happen myself,” Erica declared brightly.

Hero or not, as the ruler of the kingdom, Francois could no longer hold his silence in the face of such disrespect. “You’re saying you will use force to abolish my kingdom’s monarchy and nobility system? Shall I take that as a declaration of war from the Holy Democratic Republic of Erica?” he asked with a sharp look.

“Now that things have come to this, I suppose so? Did you want me to make a clearer act of hostility?”

“What...?”

“Hee hee. As I said earlier, I’m from a small nation. You’re a major kingdom. Perhaps it would be better to take one more hostage,” Erica said.

She turned to look at Charlotte, who was standing with the others by the wall. The next moment, she was on her feet and sprinting forward, materializing her Divine Arms while approaching Charlotte.

“...”

Before Erica could pin Charlotte from behind, Rio had grabbed her bishop’s staff and stood before her.

“...Hm?”

Erica pushed her staff forward, intending on sending Rio flying together with Charlotte behind him. However, Rio had enhanced his body and held his ground against her physical strength. They were both putting a rather large amount of force into it, as their hands were trembling.

What amazing magic essence... She’s enhancing her physical body a lot.

Rio looked at Erica and analyzed her silently. Behind him, Charlotte had taken the opportunity to cling to his back, but quickly retreated to avoid getting in his way. Meanwhile...

“You’ve got quite the muscles on you. Are you a knight? How wonderful,” Erica giggled, smiling gracefully.

“What shall I do, Your Majesty?” Rio asked Francois, who was still seated.

“She’s holding Liselotte hostage... If she doesn’t aggravate things further, have her leave quietly for today.”

“Understood,” Rio nodded. “Then...”

“Oh my...”

With her staff still held in her dominant hand, Erica suddenly lost her balance and fell forward. Rio pinned the handle with both hands, restraining her from moving freely. Rio had waited for the moment Erica put more force into her push and instantly used that momentum to pull the staff towards him.

“You used the strength I put in myself...” Erica tilted her head curiously, realizing Rio had shifted his center of gravity to splendidly use her strength against her.

“As expected of a major kingdom. Be it that attendant girl or this boy here, you have quite the selection of soldiers. How wonderful indeed.” Erica looked at Rio’s face once again, then continued with a look around the room. Aria was standing before Francois, her enchanted sword ready to protect him.

“You’ve been given the option to leave without causing any further trouble,” Rio said to the saint, still holding on to her staff. He was asking whether she had any intention of causing more problems.

“Challenging you to a duel seems like a terrible effort. Though I have no intention of causing trouble...”

Erica poured magic essence into her bishop’s staff as she spoke. The magic essence flowed through the staff pressed against the floor, spreading across its entire surface.

“Guh...” Rio immediately started preparing magic essence within his body as well. At the same time, Celia and Miharu, who could visibly see magic essence, also noticed the powerful magic being charged into the staff and looked shocked.

“How about this, then?” Erica released the magic essence she had charged into her staff and tried to activate some sort of phenomenon. The staff glowed with divine light, and the floor started shining too. It was at that moment that the others realized Erica had poured magic essence into her staff, but...

“...”

Nothing happened. It was clear that Erica had tried to do something, so Francois and the others had doubtful looks on their faces. But the same applied for Erica.

“How strange... I put enough magic essence into the staff to destroy this room, but...”

“Wha...”

With her intentions revealed, the entire room was lost for words.

Erica gazed at Rio and threw out an accusation. “What did you do? Did you interfere with my Divine Arm? How did you do that?”

In reality, that was exactly what happened. Rio had used spirit arts to overwrite the phenomenon Erica had tried to manifest.

“...”

Francois and the others looked on with confusion and shock, holding their breaths. They couldn’t understand what was going on, but they could tell a high-level battle was occurring between Rio and the saint before them.

“If you’re ignoring His Majesty’s words to aggravate the situation, should I assume you will not be returning quietly?”

Rio returned Erica’s aggression with a sharp gaze. His words were polite, but his tone was chillingly cold.

“Heh. Heh heh heh. In that case, I’m sure you understand Liselotte Cretia’s safety won’t be guaranteed. If I don’t return by a certain date, my people will sentence her,” Erica threatened with a fearless smile.

“...Then it would be best for you to return quietly. If you continue to act violently and risk everyone’s safety, I will have no choice but to apprehend you.”

It’s not what I desire, but is it what you desire? Rio implied with his gaze.

“...Fine. My role right now is to bestow a revelation upon the people of this nation. I can always eliminate the people here after the people have made their fury known. No, that is the correct order. It seems I nearly messed up in my haste. Now that I’ve fulfilled my original goal, I shall take my leave here.”

The mace in Erica’s hand vanished. She proceeded to raise her hands and show she had no wish to fight, then started walking towards the door. Rio tried to follow her to make sure she didn’t try anything strange, but Erica turned around and stopped him.

“If you follow me, I may end up making a mess of this castle. I’m sure you haven’t forgotten, but Liselotte Cretia is in my hands right now.”

As a result, Rio had no choice but to come to a halt. Everyone else’s angered gazes focused on Erica’s back, infuriated by how they couldn’t chase after her.

Eventually, Erica left the room, and as soon as the door shut, Rio spoke up.

“Your Majesty, please give me permission to pursue her,” he said to Francois.

“What...?”

Francois was wide-eyed.

“If we allow that saint to escape here, Liselotte might never return to us. I will pin down her location and retrieve her.” There was no hesitation in his eyes. He would save her. His determination was clear.

“Hmm... But you absolutely cannot be detected while pursuing her to find Liselotte’s location. Can you do that?”

The moment he was discovered, Liselotte would most likely never return again. Francois hummed in thought while staring at Rio but seemed to believe it would be possible if it were him.

“I can stalk her while maintaining a one-kilometer distance. If I go too far, I’ll lose sight of her, but I have a means of never losing sight of her within that distance. That’s why there’s a little leeway in time, but please make a decision soon,” Rio answered.

Aishia, it’s an emergency. Stay in your spirit form and follow the black-haired woman about to leave the castle.

At the same time, he called out to Aishia telepathically without waiting for Francois’s permission.

Got it, came her immediate reply.

Thanks.

All that was left was to actually set off after her. Rio looked straight at Francois and waited for his answer.

“There’s one thing I’d like to ask of Lady Satsuki.”

“What is it?”

“If the saint takes an aggressive stance, will you be willing to make an official statement as a hero that our kingdom was not at fault?” Francois asked, seeking her assistance.

The Strahl region viewed the heroes as sacred beings, so if things were to take a serious turn with a hero, they’d need another hero on their side. As someone burdened with the welfare of a kingdom, this was something he had to confirm first.

“Of course. You don’t even need to ask. There’s no way I’d forgive someone like that.” Satsuki must have made up her mind about the saint, as her reply was instant.

“All right... Then Liselotte’s rescue shall be left to Haruto. Fine with you, Cedric?”

Francois nodded deeply, giving Rio permission to rescue Liselotte. He then turned to Liselotte’s father, Cedric, for confirmation.

“Please take care of this, Haruto.” Cedric closed his eyes uneasily but ultimately bowed his head.

“I will do my best.”

“We’re counting on you,” Francois said, entrusting everything to Rio.

“And so, please explain everything to the others for me.” Rio nodded deeply in response to Francois, then turned to Miharu, Celia, Satsuki, and Charlotte beside him to rely on them for the rest.

“Yup... Be careful.”

“Make sure you come back safely.”

“Please take care of Liselotte, Haruto.”

Celia, Miharu, and Satsuki looked at Rio with worry.

“I shall await your return, Sir Haruto.” Charlotte pinched the hem of her dress up and saw Rio off resolutely.

“Leave it to me. I’ll definitely bring her back.” Rio smiled to reassure the four of them, then started walking out of the room to go after the saint.

“Wait.”

“What is it?”

Just before he left the room, Francois called for him to stop. Rio paused before the door.

“We’ve basically been handed a clear declaration of war. Lady Satsuki has also given her seal of approval. It no longer matters whether our opponent is a hero or a saint. If they pursue you after the rescue, you may use your own discretion to act. Bring out all of your strength if you need to.”

Make them regret picking a fight with us—Francois gave permission for Rio to cross swords with the saint as though to say exactly that. The fact it was coming from the king himself also had huge implications.

“Understood.” Rio bowed his head deeply and left the room.

“If I may please make a request unworthy of my standing.” The voice of a woman echoed in the meeting room.

Epilogue: Companion

After leaving the meeting room, Rio walked leisurely towards the entrance of the castle so that he wouldn’t catch up to Erica. Along the way, he confirmed with the knights that she had passed by.

Haruto, a black-haired woman is approaching the gate. I’ll continue to follow her after she leaves.

Then, Aishia made contact.

Apparently she really was going to leave the castle quietly.

Thank you. Let me know if anything happens. I’ll follow within range of our telepathic connection.

Got it.

Rio made his way out of the castle while communicating with her. Saint Erica should have been going through the castle gate two hundred meters in front of him right now.

“Please wait!”

Just at that moment, a voice called out from behind Rio, and its owner ran up to him. She must have been in a hurry, as she was breathing a little heavily.

“Aria...?”

Rio’s eyes widened. He was surprised by the fact she had chased after him, but what was more surprising was her clothes. Instead of her usual attendant’s uniform, she was dressed in what looked like adventurer clothes. Why?

“I’m begging you,” Aria began with a serious expression.

“For what...?”

Rio had a hunch what her request would be. And while he was thinking about whether that request was right or not...

“Please allow me to accompany you on the mission to rescue Lady Liselotte.”

Aria bowed her head low before Rio, pleading.